{
    "questions": [{
    "problem": "The product of a²b4 and a³b5 is",

    "choice1": "a10 b20",
    "choice2": "a5 b9",
    "choice3": "a4 b6",
    "choice4": "a6 b7",
    "correctanswer": "2"
},{
    "problem": " The product of y7 and y³ is equal to",

    "choice1": "y10",
    "choice2": "y21",
    "choice3": "y4",
    "choice4": "y²",
    "correctanswer": "1"
},
{
    "problem": "The answer of 9.5 x 105 ⁄104 in ordinary notation is",

    "choice1": "0.95",
    "choice2": "0.095",
    "choice3": "95",
    "choice4": "0.0095",
    "correctanswer": "3"
},
{
    "problem": "If 36 ⁄27 = 3x then the value of 'x' is",

    "choice1": "3",
    "choice2": "4",
    "choice3": "5",
    "choice4": "2",
    "correctanswer": "1"
},
{
    "problem": "If (94 )2 = 3x then the value of 'x' is",

    "choice1": "14",
    "choice2": "15",
    "choice3": "16",
    "choice4": "17",
    "correctanswer": "2"
},
{
    "problem": "By solving the following (5a²b³)², the answer will be",

    "choice1": "25a5 b6",
    "choice2": "25a4 b6",
    "choice3": "25a7 b5",
    "choice4": "25a³b4",
    "correctanswer": "2"
},
{
    "problem": "By solving a x (a²)9 , the answer will be",

    "choice1": "a15",
    "choice2": "a19",
    "choice3": "a18",
    "choice4": "a20",
    "correctanswer": "2"
},
{
    "problem": " By evaluating the (4⁄5)-2 ⁄(3)0 , the result will be",

    "choice1": "1⁄16",
    "choice2": "25⁄16",
    "choice3": "16⁄25",
    "choice4": "1⁄25",
    "correctanswer": "2"
},
{
    "problem": "On evaluating the (512)1⁄3 , the answer will be",

    "choice1": "1⁄4",
    "choice2": "1⁄2",
    "choice3": "8",
    "choice4": "1⁄8",
    "correctanswer": "3"
},
{
    "problem": "By simplifying (3x5 y6 )4 ⁄(3x4 y6 )³, the answer will be",

    "choice1": "3x8 y6",
    "choice2": "3x5 y7",
    "choice3": "3x9 y5",
    "choice4": "3x10 y4",
    "correctanswer": "1"
}]}